From the outside, it looks simple.
Dall'esterno, sembra semplice.
You confiscate the money, count it, and hand it over.
Confischi i soldi, li conti e li consegni.
Knock, knock, Miami police.
Toc, toc, polizia di Miami.
From the inside, it's different.
Dall'interno, è diverso.
An anonymous tip led us to this address.
Una soffiata anonima ci ha indicato questo indirizzo.
- Oh, shit. - There's 1.4 million in here.
- Oh, merda. - Qua dentro ci sono 1,4 milioni.
I saw at least 14 other buckets.
Io ho visto almeno altri 14 secchi.
It's a 20 million seizure.
È un sequestro da 20 milioni.
We need to be cautious. Let's get the money out of here.
Ci vuole cautela. Portiamo i soldi via da qui.
Turn off the radios. No calls.
Spegnete le radio. Nessuna chiamata.
What would you do with this?
Che faresti con questi?
Just this.
Solo questi.
Everything.
Tutto.
You've heard about the robbery squads.
Hai sentito delle squadre di rapina.
Cops playing robbers.
Poliziotti che giocano a fare i rapinatori.
- Do you need help, Lieutenant? - No.
- Ha bisogno di aiuto, tenente? - No.
No one warned us.
Nessuno ci ha avvisati.
The longer we stay here, the more we risk ending up in deep shit.
Più restiamo qui, più rischiamo di finire nella merda.
Don't trust anyone.
Non fidarti di nessuno.
I just know that what we do now and who we talk to matters.
So solo che quello che facciamo ora e con chi parliamo è importante.
Did you see?
Hai visto?
C-O-P-S.
S-B-I-R-R-I.
You have 30 minutes to get out of that house.
Avete 30 minuti per uscire da quella casa.
By any chance, did you hear anything about him?
Per caso hai saputo qualcosa su di lui?
There are fucking moles in every division.
Ci sono talpe del cazzo in ogni divisione.
Watch your back.
Guardati le spalle.
- Down! - The fence!
- Giù! - Lo steccato!
- I'm going over there! - I'll take the roof.
- Vado di là! - Io penso al tetto.
You want to steal this money, Dane? Why don't you admit it?
Vuoi rubare questi soldi, Dane? Perché non lo ammetti?
Are you a snitch, Mike?
Sei un infame, Mike?
This is my scene. Let me handle it.
Questa è la mia scena. Lascia fare a me.
Are you leaving with that money?
Vai via con quei soldi?
Were you and Captain Velez close?
Lei e il capitano Velez eravate legati?
What's your problem?
Che problemi hai?
What the fuck is going on?
Che cazzo succede?
First of all, calm down.
Prima di tutto, datti una calmata.
No, no, no. You're not going anywhere.
No, no, no. Tu non vai da nessuna parte.
I don't take orders from you.
Non prendo ordini da te.
I don't trust you right now, and that's a fucking problem!
Io non mi fido di te al momento, ed è un cazzo di problema!
Take whatever money you want and leave.
Prendete i soldi che volete e andatevene.
Before things end badly for all of us.
Prima che qui finisca male per tutti noi.